Hello.
妳好
Nice to meet you. You must be Kasane.
初次見面妳好 妳就是重吧
I'm Naomi.
我是直見
From now on, we'll be sisters.
從今天起我們就是姊妹了
I'm your elder sister, and you're my little sister.
我是姊姊 重是妹妹
I hope we get along, Kasane.
請多指教囉 重
Sister...
姊…姊…
SCARLET NEXUS
《緋紅結繫》
♪A crime in reality♪
現實的Crime
♪For Heaven's sake♪
For Heaven's sake
♪Accepts any fake♪
接受虛假
♪And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♪
永恆的幻想 層層逝去
♪Won't take it at all, I get sick♪
絕非完美 I get sick
♪A girl looking back♪
轉身而來的少女
♪Casts the miracle into the instant world♪
在這瞬息世界中 落下了奇蹟
♪Did you lie♪
Did you lie
♪Spit the venom♪
Spit the venom
♪I know why♪
I know why
♪I've found a game of ecstasy♪
找到了 絕頂的遊戲
♪Red Criminal gets life♪
Red Criminal gets life
♪I've never been in love♪
I've never been in love
♪Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♪
我何時開始厭倦了這樣的世界
♪We will fly♪
We will fly
♪Someday I won't be crying♪
Someday I won't be crying
♪I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♪
為了不再傷害 而犧牲了自己
CONSPIRACY
(陰謀)
Sister...
姊姊…
Kasane!
重
Do not undo the Red String.
別解開紅色繫線
I want all available fighters here!
能動的人都過來幫忙
Nagi!
那歧
Nagi, are you all right?
那歧 你沒事吧
Sister!
姊姊
Kasane...
重
Stop it!
住手
If you don't...
再不住手…
Wait! Sister!
等等 姊姊
Sister!
姊姊
Don't go over there.
別過去
Let go of me! Naomi...
放開我 直見 直見她…
What happened just now
剛才…是怎麼回事
Naomi is...
直見她竟然…
This can't be happening...
怎麼會
-Let me go! -Gemma.
-放開我 -蓋曼
I'm glad you're all right.
各位 還好你們沒事
Major General Fubuki.
吹雪連隊長
Seto and Kyoka are safe.
賽特和鏡花他們也沒事
We eliminated all Others.
所有怪異都清除了
What matters now is...
現在重要的是…
It was Naomi, am I right?
直見對吧
Everyone, do not tell anyone what you witnessed today.
各位 今天看到的景象 請別對外宣傳
What do you mean?
什麼意思
I meant what I said.
就是字面上的意思
This is for your safety.
這麼做是為了保護你們
Our safety?
保護我們
What about Naomi?
可是…直見呢
Naomi...
直見…
I'll report Naomi's disappearance as killed in action.
由我提出直見戰死的報告
Killed in action?
戰死
This isn't right.
怎麼這樣
Naomi is still alive.
直見沒有死
Understood.
我知道了
Gemma!
蓋曼
This is an order from the Major General.
這是連隊長的命令
Sorry, Gemma.
抱歉 蓋曼
Hold on, Kasane.
重 回來
Where are you going?
妳要去哪
The mission is still ongoing. Do not wander off on your own.
現在還在作戰中 請勿擅自行動
Kasane!
重
Fubuki. I should get going.
吹雪 先走了
Very well.
好
Nagi seems injured.
那歧似乎受傷了
Take him to a hospital.
帶他去醫院吧
Gemma, I leave the rest to you.
蓋曼 交給你了
Understood.
好的
Tsugumi, look after Kasane.
鶇 重交給妳照顧
Naomi was strong and gentle.
直見 是堅強又溫柔的女孩
Why...
卻…
Loss is inevitable as long as we're a member of the OSF.
只要在怪伐軍裡一天 就會面臨這種別離
We can only do our best to cope.
只能努力跨越嗎…
Cursed Others.
可惡的怪異
When you die, you can't slack off again.
死了 就無法再偷懶了
Kasane.
重
A member of OSF...
竟然是怪伐軍的隊員
To make it worse, Yuito saw it.
而且還是被結人他們…
Leave them to me.
他們 就交給我處理吧
Not a word will get out.
決不會外傳
Very well. I'm counting on you.
好吧 就交給你處理
Major General Spring.
詩賓少將
Thank you for your trust.
謝謝
Sister...
姊姊…
NEW MESSAGE. DO YOU WISH TO PLAY IT?
(收到簡訊 要播放嗎)
I was told Naomi died in the battle.
我收到直見戰死的消息了
Why didn't you tell me?
妳為何不跟我說
Our dear Naomi...
我們所疼愛的直見…
We couldn't turn down the recruitment.
我們無法拒絕國家招募
We left Naomi in your care.
所以只好將直見託付給妳
We were wrong about you.
是我們看錯人了
It was foolish to trust you.
是我們太笨了
From now on, do not contact us again.
以後 妳也不用再跟我們聯絡了
Are you going to report what happened to Naomi?
妳打算去報告直見的事嗎
Seiran took Naomi.
是青藍帶走了直見
For Naomi to become human again,
為了讓直見變回人類
we must rely on them.
只能拜託他們了
They will not kill Naomi right away.
他們不會殺死直見的
You have my word.
我跟妳保證
She can become human again?
變回人類
You have no idea what happened.
你根本就不知道發生什麼事
Yet you want me to trust you.
卻要我相信你
You don't understand what happened to her,
妳根本就不知道發生什麼事
yet you doubt my words.
卻懷疑我所說的話
Even if you managed to get her back,
就算妳現在奪回了直見
she will be terminated as an Other.
她也只會被視為怪異而喪命
You must keep this incident a secret.
這次的事 絕不能對外宣傳
Otherwise, not just Naomi,
否則 不只是直見
even your life would be in danger.
我甚至無法保證妳的存在
Are you going to kill me?
打算殺了我嗎
I don't think they would
我想他們應該…
actually kill you.
不會"殺了妳"
Do not trust the people of New Himuka.
別相信新日向的這幫人
Kasane? Are you all right?
重 妳沒事了嗎
You were there when it happened.
你當時也在場
I guess telling you shouldn't be considered treason.
跟你說的話 也不算是對外宣傳
Seiran took Naomi?
直見被青藍帶走了
What is the OSF hiding from us?
怪伐軍似乎隱瞞些什麼
Right.
對了
Perhaps this has something to do with it.
不知道這個是否有關連
Let me show you.
我想給妳看看
Wait! I kept it in here.
不是啦 我放在裡面
Ampoule?
安瓿
I found them by the abandoned tracks.
掉在廢棄地下軌道
It could be some sort of drugs.
是不是某種藥
It has the mark of Seiran City on it.
上面印著青藍市的標誌
I've seen this before.
這個…我好像在哪看過
At your home?
妳家嗎
Why would they have this?
為何會有這個東西
It could be a clue.
這或許是個線索
It'd be best if you didn't tell anyone.
盡量別被別人知道
Very well.
好
As for Naomi...
直見的事…
I'm sorry.
對不起
I knew that monster was Naomi.
我知道那隻怪異就是直見
-But I... -Enough!
-可我… -別說了
I'll bring her back.
我會奪回直見
Just don't get in my way.
只要你不妨礙我就好
I know this might be fancy words to you,
或許我說的只是場面話
but I want to help too.
但我也願意盡力幫忙
Those are fancy words indeed.
確實是場面話
But I appreciate it./
不過…謝謝你
How is Nagi?
對了 那歧還好嗎
I lost contact with him after they rushed him to a hospital.
他被帶到醫院後 我就連絡不上了
He was a volunteer just like me.
他跟我一樣是志願入伍
We went to the same training school.
上同一間訓練學校
But because of my family, people treated me like I was special.
因為我是皇家人 無論到哪都會被視為特別的存在
Only Nagi treated me like a normal person.
只有那歧 像平常一樣跟我相處
Well, that wasn't very normal after all.
不 其實也不平常
I'd say he was overly friendly.
應該說 過於親近吧
But I couldn't have come this far without him.
不過 因為有那歧 才有現在的我
Nice to meet you, Kasane.
請多指教 重
Kasane.
重
Captain Seto.
賽特隊長
How are you holding up?
妳沒問題了嗎
I'm fine.
是的
Are you sure? Don't push yourself too hard.
真的嗎 不要勉強喔
I'll be fine. Thank you for your concern.
我沒事的 讓隊長擔心了
I'm not concerned about you.
我不是在擔心妳
When you push yourself too hard in a battle,
在戰場上 如果有人過於勉強自己
you put your comrades in danger.
會害同伴陷入困境
You're not fighting alone.
妳不是一個人
Don't forget, you still have those in the Kyoka Platoon.
別忘了 還有鏡花小隊的成員在
Yes.
是
I'm glad you understand.
妳能理解就好
I should get going.
先走了
Are you sure about this?
真的沒問題嗎
Don't worry.
放心吧
This is a blind spot for the surveillance system.
這裡是監視系統的死角
The preparation is almost complete.
我們快準備好了
What about our plan to take down OSF?
瓦解怪伐軍的狀況如何
Proceed as usual.
照計畫進行中
This country will be ours...
這個國家 將由我們…
What? How is this happening?
什麼 怎麼會這樣
An alarm of unprecedented scale has been announced.
怪異省發布 以往從未有過的大量怪異警報
The location is centered around a ten-kilometer radius
地點是以岐高速運輸公路為中心
of the Kunad Highway.
半徑十公里內
All soldiers of the OSF will be deployed.
怪伐軍 全軍出動討伐怪異
We've issued an evacuation order to citizens of the Suoh capital.
已對蘇芳京的市民發出避難指示
-Hurry up! -Get to the shelter.
-動作快 -快去避難
-They are overreacting. -The monsters are in Kunad, not here.
-大驚小怪的 -怪異出現在岐 又不是這裡
Get to the shelter!
快去避難
All members, deploy!
全軍 出動
Hinokami Platoon, move out.
水上隊 前進
Sakaki Platoon, move out.
榊隊 前進
Kyoka, see you there.
鏡花 現場會合
Yes. Watch your back.
好 你多加小心
Where is Gemma going?
蓋曼去哪
The Others came in large numbers.
這次的怪異數量較多
He was assigned to command a special platoon.
他被派去指揮特別編列的機動隊
That must be a lot of work.
真是辛苦他了
Kageru.
陽炎
It's nothing. I'm simply excited.
沒事 我只是躍躍欲試而已
Kasane, are you all right?
重 妳還好嗎
I'll be fine. I'll follow Captain Seto's order and not overdo myself.
沒事 我會如賽特隊長說的 不勉強自己
I can't die before I get Naomi back.
在奪回直見之前 我是不會死的
Great.
那就好
Captain Seto, everyone!
賽特隊長 各位
Nagi?
那歧
You're discharged, great.
太好了 你出院啦
How is your injury?
你沒事了嗎
Why would you say that, Tsugumi?
鶇 怎麼這麼說
Are you worried about me?
妳這麼擔心我啊
Oh my!
真傷腦筋
Captain Seto.
賽特隊長
Private Nagi Karman
那歧卡門上等兵
reporting to duty.
返回執行任務
We're glad you're back. Everyone was waiting for you.
回來就好 大家都在等你
Going back into action right after his discharge.
一出院就上戰場啊
The army can be really harsh sometimes.
怪伐軍真會使喚人啊
I need to stretch my limbs anyway. I'll take this as my rehab therapy.
再不活動身體都要生鏽了 正好當作復健
Nagi...
那歧…
Welcome back.
歡迎回來
But let's save the chitchat for later.
但聊天到此結束吧
-Let's go. -Yes.
-上吧 -是
Nagi, are you sure you'd be fine?
那歧 你真的沒事了嗎
My injury is almost healed.
傷勢已經好得差不多了
See?
你看
No, I meant what happened to Naomi...
不是啦 我是說直見的事…
I'm still not over Naomi's death.
直見戰死的事的確讓我大受打擊
But I can't keep sulking.
不過 我也不能一直消沉下去
Naomi's death?
戰死
Naomi is still alive.
直見還活著喔
I know it's weird that she was turned into an Other...
雖然 變成怪異而活著 是有點奇怪…
What do you mean?
你在說什麼啊
What do you mean she turned into an Other?
變成怪異 什麼意思啊
You shouldn't joke about something so serious.
你最好別亂開這種玩笑
What if Kasane heard it?
被重聽到了怎麼辦
We will continue to fight the Others for the sake of New Himuka.
我們接下來要為新日向 與怪異戰鬥
It will be tough, but we must keep moving forward.
雖然很辛苦 但還是要繼續往前進
All right, let's go.
好了 走吧
Nagi, what happened to you?
那歧 你到底怎麼了
Captain Seto.
賽特隊長
We should head to the forecast locations now.
我們差不多到了預報說的地點吧
We've met a few of them before...
到此之前 雖然遇到幾隻怪異
but not in this number.
但數量應該不止這些吧
We could get off work early if there weren't many of them.
只有這些的話 那就能提早回去了
Indeed, it's too quiet here.
的確 這裡安靜過頭了
Wataru.
渡
How is the surrounding area?
四周狀況如何
This is different from the forecast.
的確跟怪異預報有所出入
Could there be an error?
是哪裡弄錯了嗎
I'll confirm the Other attacks...
我現在馬上確認怪異…
Wataru? What's wrong, Wataru?
渡 怎麼了
Haruka?
遙…
Captain Seto, please respond.
賽特隊長 請回答
Captain?
隊長
Brother.
哥哥
I can't get a hold of Captain Kyoka either.
我也連絡不上鏡花隊長
What? Could it be...
什麼 難道是…
It's a jamming signal.
訊號被干擾了
Tsugumi?
鶇
Captain, we've been surrounded!
隊長 我們被包圍了
Those are OSF soldiers.
那是…怪伐軍
Were there other platoons
除了我們之外
that were sent to this location?
還派了其他小隊到這個地點嗎
Gemma?
蓋曼
Gemma, what is this about?
蓋曼 你要幹嘛
We could go home early today.
難得能早點回去
Don't you dare give us more work.
你可別增加我們的工作
Gemma, what is going on?
蓋曼 這是怎麼回事
Sorry, Kyoka.
抱歉 鏡花
Seto, I can't believe you've done such a horrible experiment.
賽特 沒想到你做了 如此恐怖的研究
What do you mean?
你在說什麼
You can stop pretending now.
你想裝傻嗎
What are you talking about? What do you want?
你到底在說什麼 又在做什麼
I'm confused.
這是怎麼回事
All of you, stand back.
你們最好盡快退下
Luka...
魯卡
Luka Travers!
魯卡崔佛斯
Do you think you can handle two Septentrions at once?
你們以為贏得過兩位七劍星嗎
Luka, what is going on here?
魯卡 這到底是怎麼回事
I'll explain later.
之後再跟你解釋
Let me take care of these soldiers.
我來擊退這些怪伐軍
-Run while you... -If I'm your opponent,
-你們趁機逃… -我來當你的對手
will you still be as confident?
你還說得出同樣的話嗎
Major General!
連隊長
Brother!
哥哥
Luka, you've come at last.
魯卡 你果然還是來了
Everyone, I'll handle him.
各位 哥哥交給我來對付
Ignorance!
天真
Brain field!
腦內空間
Sclerokinesis, electrokinesis, and aerokinesis...
又是硬質化又是放電又是空氣操作
Don't you remember?
你忘了嗎
He can copy people's powers and use them as his own!
連隊長能複製別人的腦力 化為自己的攻擊
A brain eater.
噬腦…者…
Major General Karen.
卡連連隊長
Are you the mastermind behind this?
一切都是你算計的嗎
This country...
這個國家…
New Himuka has lied to you!
新日向欺騙了我們
Gemma.
蓋曼
My sister...
你知道我姊姊…
You know what happened to Naomi!
知道直見發生什麼事了嗎
-Naomi? -What do you mean?
-直見 -妳在說什麼啊
I knew it.
果然…
The New Himuka Government is involved.
跟新日向…跟政府有關…
Kasane!
重
Kasane, what do you mean?
重 妳說什麼
Answer me...
回答我
Answer me, Gemma!
蓋曼 回答我
♪I don't need to let fate dictate me♪
無須被命運所指使
♪Because I believe that I can rewrite it♪
相信定會被改寫
♪I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♪
讓我們今後 繼續做著夢
♪Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♪
朝陽正光輝燦爛 隨後落下
♪What's waiting for us at the world's end♪
在世界的盡頭 究竟等著什麼
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going♪
未來 燈火永恆不滅
♪Who can shake us♪
誰在威脅我們
♪Who can define us♪
誰為我們決定
♪It's nothing less than our story♪
這是屬於我們的故事
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♪
未來 你心中的燈火永恆不滅
RED STRINGS
(紅色繫線)